(Arthur:)Trust me, I... I remember.
(Sheldon:)This is my girlfriend, Amy.
(Sheldon:)Amy, this is television
legend Arthur Jeffries.
(Sheldon:)His science show
inspired millions of children.
(Arthur:)Hold... Hold on.
(Arthur:)You... You have a girlfriend?
(Amy:)Yes, and I've heard
so much about you.
(Amy:)Hey, look, we're wearing
the same orthopedic shoes.
(Amy:)I can't believe I dress
like a celebrity.
(Arthur:)Okay, I get it now.
(Leonard:)Dr. Jeffries, hello again.
Leonard Hofstadter.
(Arthur:)Oh, oh, right,
I remember your girlfriend.
(Arthur:)Is she... is she here?
(Leonard:)No, she's not.
(Sheldon:)So, what prescription
are you getting filled?
(Sheldon:)-Sheldon.
-No. Wait, I want to guess.
(Sheldon:)Don't tell me.
(Arthur:)I wasn't going to tell you.
(Amy:)Sheldon, come on.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no. I'm really good at this.
All right, give me a hint.
(Sheldon:)Does it involve difficulty initiating
a stream of anything?
(Arthur:)Well, given my age,
thats more than just a lucky guess.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon,
let's go mock the people
(Leonard:)buying homeopathic medicine.
You love that.
(Sheldon:)But I'm hanging out with my friend,
and we're having fun.
Look how happy he ls.